<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Blog Title</title>
  <subtitle>This is a longer description about your blog.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://example.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://example.com/" />
  <updated>2025-11-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://example.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Your Name</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>September - O</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/September-%20Owen/" />
    <updated>2025-11-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/September-%20Owen/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;As part of my post-move effort to leave the house and talk to people I recently read the book “The Lion Women of Tehran” by Marjan Kamali in preparation for a book club discussion at a local book store (which I have since learned is owned by and basically just a Barnes &amp;amp; Noble). I thought the book was fine, and I don’t think the book club will be a long term join for me, but it did inspire me to make a new-to-me kind of sandwich.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Food is a major through line  in the book, with one particularly compelling example being the “Salad-Olivier” sandwich which the main characters frequently get at bustling cafes in Tehran. I decided to fulfill my September prompt by making this sandwich for a couple reasons. First, I love a mayonnaise based sandwich and this one is basically a combination of egg, potato, and chicken so how could that be bad. Second, It also had a lot of frozen peas in it which is fun. Finally and most importantly, it seemed pretty easy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to up the difficulty level I also decided to make my own baguettes. A process which took a long time and at no point in the process did I believe it would actually work. In the end the baguettes turned out basically okay (far better than expected), but probably not really worth the effort. The salad itself was pretty nice, kinda exactly what you would expect based on the recipe. If I were to make it again I would probably back off on the potato a bit, especially in the sandwich context if felt very dense and heavy. I think my main takeaway from this experience was that you can put a bunch of peas into your egg or tuna salad.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>October - O</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/October%20-%20Owen/" />
    <updated>2025-11-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/October%20-%20Owen/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Colfax Avenue is a 50 mile main street running through the Denver Metropolitan area and considered the “longest continuous commercial street in the United States” according to Wikipedia and no further research on my part. It seemed like the most obvious long straight line in the area for me to walk, so I took the bus about 5 miles east to the Denver/Aurora border and walked back home straight down Colfax.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Colfax’s reputation in the Denver area (especially East Colfax in the direction of Aurora) is far from stellar. If you google “Colfax Reddit” you’ll see plenty of people concerned about safety around the street and people complaining about the seemingly never ending construction. In terms of safety I think that is the classic Redditor response to areas where homeless people and people using drugs tend to congregate, and in my walk I never felt anything I would describe as dangerous. The construction is a much more real concern for me, but it will in theory result in a rapid transit bus line which is exciting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started at the intersection of Clinton and Colfax headed west with a view of the mountains far off in the distance. For the first couple of miles mostly what I passed was motels. There are more motels along this stretch of road than I think I have ever seen in such a small area, Remnants of when this was the main auto route through the area. Some were open, a few were closed and boarded up, all of them had signs warning against drug dealing, prostitution, and any unregistered guests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Along with motels this stretch of road featured a handful of Mexican restaurants, markets, and food trucks. Despite it approaching the end of October the sun was still beating down hard and I found myself hot and thirsty. I detoured (ever so slightly) from my straight line to a taco truck to quench my thirst with a fresh Pineapple aqua Fresca. The drink was basically pineapple juice, so nothing too exciting, but it was cold and refreshing and not too sweet. The truck also sold a regional taco variant called “tacos al vapor” which I’ll be back to try sometime soon. Tree cover or any noticeable shade continued to be dearly missed, but with my reapplied sunscreen and aqua fresca in hand I kept on down the road.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next couple of miles were generally nondescript with a few places jumping out as being a bit more interesting. Lots of closed up buildings and a variety of auto shops. One strip stood for featuring a handful of Ethiopian restaurants. Another building advertised a fencing and modern pentathlon training center. I don’t think I knew modern pentathlon was a thing, and if I did I certainly wouldn’t have known fencing was one of its disciplines. Another restaurant that has jumped high in my “need to visit” list was a Moroccan place called “Couscous hice a break from rice” which featured a picture of Gordan Ramsay out front next a sign indicating that Moroccan food had been voted the best in the world in 2024.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I didn’t interact with many people along my walk. Folks tended to be hanging out on side streets where a bit of shad could be found. Halfway through my walk I did help a guy with a dead phone find the clinic where he was supposed to get his medical marijuana card was located. A bit later when I was about a mile out from my house I suddenly found myself surrounded by costumed children and chaperones participating in a Halloween block party. The hustle bustle of kids running from store to store getting candy heightened the already stark difference between the quiet and shuttered up East Colfax and the generally lively less-East Colfax.  From here out I was in more familiar territory, passing by the shop I bought my new bike from, the book store I’ve been to a couple disappointing book clubs at, and the park that hosts my local farmers market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Returning home I can’t say I had a perspective altering experience. I’ve always been fond of the restaurants and grocery stores that are often found in the ethnic neighborhoods on the outskirts of towns, and I’ve never found myself particularly worried about finding myself in what other people may describe as the “bad parts” of town (maybe I should be a bit more aware than I am). If I had the time I’d like to continue my walk further west and see how the street changes as it passes through downtown and ever closer to the mountains in the distance. Maybe a continuation for another day.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>August - O</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/2025-09-14%20O/" />
    <updated>2025-09-14T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/2025-09-14%20O/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-top-10-greatest-one-hit-wonders-of-the-80s&quot;&gt;The Top 10 Greatest One Hit Wonders of the 80&#39;s&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;as-sourced-from-vh1-classics-top-100-greatest-one-hit-wonders-of-the-80s&quot;&gt;As sourced from VH1 Classic&#39;s Top 100 Greatest One Hit Wonders of The 80&#39;s&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the March 31st  episode of VH1’s “The Greatest” series Judah Friedlander oversaw a countdown of the 100 Greatest One Hit Wonders of the 80s. (The previous episode was on the 40 Greatest Celebrity Divorces and the following episode was the 40 Naughtiest Celebrity Scandals). Following the release you could aptly describe my taste in music as “VH1’s The 100 Greatest One Hit Wonders of the 80’s”. Initially I had planned on doing my own re-ranking of the full list of 100 songs, but that would be hard so instead here are my top 10 Greatest One Hit Wonders of the 80’s:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear God - XTC&lt;/strong&gt;:
This song is kinda cheesy (an important element of many one hit wonders), but I’m a bit of a sucker for a song where a child sings (big shoutout to the Langley Schools project).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Angel Eyes - The Jeff Healey Band&lt;/strong&gt;:
There is something about a really straightforward uncomplicated ballad that is hits. This one also has some nice guitar playing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Missing You - John Waite&lt;/strong&gt;:
And then at the end.. real quiet… he says “I can lie to myself” because that’s the thing: he really is missing her.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Take on Me - A-ha&lt;/strong&gt;:
This is probably the platonic ideal example of an 80’s one hit wonder. It’s got an iconic music video, kinda annoying synths and it’s kinda unclear what it means.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our House - Madness&lt;/strong&gt;:
This is the only song on the list to feature that heavy heavy monster sound.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In a Big Country - Big Country&lt;/strong&gt;:
It’s true what they say, in a big country dreams stay with you like a lovers voice fires the mountainside.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I Melt With You - Modern English&lt;/strong&gt;:
This song kinda sounds like a a song by The Cure, which is a good thing for a song to sound like.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Buffalo Stance - Neneh Cherry&lt;/strong&gt;:
This song is very cool. It’s got scratching, a crazy synth line, an incredibly catchy chorus, and also it’s about standing in a Buffalo Stance which could mean almost anything but is undoubtedly a cool way to stand.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I Am - Edie Brickell &amp;amp; the New Bohemians&lt;/strong&gt;:
Raewyn would insist that Edie Brickell and the New Bohemian’s are not really a one hit wonder and actually have lots of bangers. I haven’t really dug into the back catalogue to confirm, but I can confirm that religion is like a smile on a dog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voices Cary - ’Til Tuesday&lt;/strong&gt;
Big shout out to Richmond Virginia’s own Amiee Mann.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>August - R</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/2025-09-07%20R/" />
    <updated>2025-09-07T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/2025-09-07%20R/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;h2 id=&quot;7-days-late-makes-one-mentally-weak&quot;&gt;7 days late makes one mentally weak&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-definitive-list-of-phrases-mentally-weak-people-often-use-in-everyday-conversation-without-realizing-it-as-compiled-by-jordan-cooper-of-vegout-mag&quot;&gt;The definitive list of phrases mentally weak people often use in everyday conversation (without realizing it), as compiled by Jordan Cooper of VegOut Mag&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&#39;t handle this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is what it is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&#39;t have time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That&#39;s just how I am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&#39;s against me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I knew I&#39;d mess it up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&#39;s not fair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&#39;s the point?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;from-at-peace-with-failure-to-close-to-a-breaking-point&quot;&gt;From &amp;quot;at peace with failure&amp;quot; to &amp;quot;close to a breaking point&amp;quot;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is what it is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That&#39;s just how I am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&#39;t have time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I knew I&#39;d mess it up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&#39;s the point?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&#39;s not fair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&#39;t handle this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&#39;s against me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;in-order-of-likelihood-of-hearing-at-a-game-night&quot;&gt;In order of likelihood of hearing at a game night&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That&#39;s just how I am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is what it is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&#39;s the point?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&#39;t handle this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I knew I&#39;d mess it up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&#39;t have time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&#39;s not fair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&#39;s against me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;in-order-of-likelihood-of-causing-a-scene-as-a-guest-at-a-wedding&quot;&gt;In order of likelihood of causing a scene as a guest at a wedding&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&#39;t have time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I knew I&#39;d mess it up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That&#39;s just how I am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&#39;s against me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is what it is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&#39;s the point?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&#39;s not fair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&#39;t handle this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;in-order-of-likelihood-of-appearing-on-a-list-of-empowering-affirmations-and-boundary-setting-phrases&quot;&gt;In order of likelihood of appearing on a list of empowering affirmations and boundary-setting phrases&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I knew I&#39;d mess it up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&#39;s against me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&#39;t handle this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&#39;s not fair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&#39;s the point?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&#39;t have time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is what it is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That&#39;s just how I am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;applicability-to-o-js-relocation&quot;&gt;Applicability to O + J&#39;s relocation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I knew I&#39;d mess it up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I can&#39;t handle this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;That&#39;s just how I am&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don&#39;t have time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Everyone&#39;s against me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&#39;s not fair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What&#39;s the point?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Whatever&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is what it is&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title></title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/2025-08-01%20-%20Owen/" />
    <updated>2025-08-01T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/2025-08-01%20-%20Owen/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;on-ducks-in-f-flat&quot;&gt;On Ducks in F Flat&lt;/h1&gt;
On sundays I workshop an upcoming matrimony of 2 mallards. &lt;br&gt;
A nuptial bond I may still unfulfill. &lt;br&gt;
Christ posits no pragmatum that  can pilot birddom to bountiful joy.&lt;br&gt;
the risk is walloping, &lt;br&gt;
which in action wants fantastic study. &lt;br&gt;Contra our frights sit hopingly a bid at joy in wildfowl fusion. &lt;br&gt;If quarral disavails this duo, what authority wouldn&#39;t attack who in act did champion up knowingly highrisk position?&lt;br&gt; Succumb to migratory wim and doom a wonderful avian to sinful union? &lt;br&gt;Absurdist plans though may triumph, &lt;br&gt;for although I nix it out &lt;br&gt;in truthful notion it wouldn&#39;t plausibly hurt bad. &lt;br&gt;Duck matrimony -frankly- should fly to our God, &lt;br&gt;wobbling in climactic aclarity.</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>July - R</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/2025-07-30/" />
    <updated>2025-07-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/2025-07-30/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;h3 id=&quot;sitting-with-quakers&quot;&gt;Sitting with Quakers&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sitting with Quakers in silence. In silence and, later, while singing. In silence or speaking or singing they suppose the presence of Light, Spirit, God. Believe this, reject it, suppose it silly or pompous… but Dillard said nothing else wrenches us nearer the sublime like silly and pompous faith. Einstein or Feynman might defy her outright, I wouldn’t dare.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Quakers live simply, I believe, and truly their potluck was bland-ish, their benches lacked cushions, their lyrics spoke plainly. The livestream is modish, I admit, and teary eyes more-ish though earnest. The simple life always seems simplest when faceless; the middle aged faces (“and better”, ha) displayed here never could suggest pure simple Faith, total Truth. Maybe a chorus of children could, although the handful of children here appeared more streetwise than angels or even their elders; the pre-teens looked lightly goth.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Perhaps some background is required to explain my presence: K*** M&lt;em&gt;G&lt;/em&gt;** crept into a meeting or two-ish in college; G***, grandma of cousins, had emailed some Quakers to shelter my tramping friends along with myself in Nelson, though revoked the request when other plans emerged. I noticed this building while walking streets around my duplex, thought about those contacts with Quakers, looked into their website, and supposed I’d attend a meeting… some later date.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Later dates often don’t arrive, but Donald bombed Iran one morning and straight-off to Meeting I hastened. The bombings sat among us; others spoke around them, implied their presence. How useful to witness the concern of neighbors! I’d wanted that. Hopeful speech (softly, one woman spoke about light waiting at tunnel’s end, about faith throughout the scary, dark middle) but also just concerned, just aware.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The H***&lt;em&gt;s&lt;/em&gt;s’ state’s very much separate from churches; we’ve never prayed, never read Bibles, and never filed into pews. Being so worldly is awesome, for many a reason -- free Sundays is surely one. Being raised without God doesn’t mean without shared values: the values my parents hold closely come blaring from nightly talk programs back inside my childhood home, hardly a secret. Still, sometimes I wonder what neighbors think, strangers too. Many things never get discussed, there’s never a venue or reason. It appears that churches are places that people air values; I value that, even though clearly some values are stupid, and others are abused or professed but ignored in practice. Well, Quakers don’t blabber but certain points landed, they landed well, spirits seemed kindred.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An hour in, Meeting was ended with handshakes, “good mornings” to pewmates. A second (brief) meeting then began: some events were announced, prayer requests made, intros were performed (three newbies, me among them). Business took hardly ten minutes, then mingling, then potluck. While potluck prep happened, one Quaker (who married his husband here twenty years ago) showed little lost newbies all around the meeting house.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Although it hasn’t yet happened I suspect that someday I’ll return, and meanwhile I’m happy just knowing it happens blocks away each Sunday, and knowing I’m welcome there, welcome with empty hands, even at potlucks.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/2025-07-26/" />
    <updated>2025-07-26T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/2025-07-26/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Orb Corporation will produce a series of blog posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>